https://www.marketingcharts.com/privacy

Subscribe[Tabs][Custom]MarketingCharts’ Privacy PolicyMarketing Charts Privacy PolicyWe are as mad at spam as you are. We get tons of it ourselves and wouldn’t even imagine adding to this constant barrage of unsolicited bulk email. So our privacy policy is quite simple: we won’t use your email address for any other purpose than the one for which you originally gave it to us: sending you our newsletter and sponsorship content. This may include contacting subscribers to update information once in a while, and, from time to time, inviting some readers to participate in a readership survey. Occasionally we also notify our readers of relevant events and products.About Our NewsletterSubscribers receive our newsletter three times a week, on Mondays, Wednesdays and Fridays. The newsletter contains our latest charts and articles, along with short analyses and highlights.Subscribers also receive a promotional email featuring a sponsored download each Tuesday. We receive payments from sponsors for sending these download offers, and they are our primary form of monetization currently, as we believe our subscribers derive real value from the curated download offers – more so than by cluttering our pages with display ads.As a subscriber, each email you receive will contain options to manage your preferences and/or unsubscribe.Your Name and E-Mail AddressWe won’t rent, swap or sell our lists to advertisers, other web sites or list brokers. We may engage in co-registration deals with other publishers, provided these partnerships are based on opt-in (i.e. you won’t get anything from our partners unless you actively choose to).We consider our lists a business asset and we reserve the right to sell them if someone was to acquire one of our newsletters. Any potential acquirer would have to commit to respecting this privacy policy and change it only with your active consent.The Information We HoldSiteWe do not capture any personal identification information on our site visitors, only anonymous information as detailed in the sections below this one.NewsletterWe currently use MailChimp as our email marketing and automation service provider. Within MailChimp we hold the following data:Information that newsletter subscribers may have provided when they opted in. This may include First and Last Name, Email Address, Phone Number, Job Title, Organization, Company Size, and Country. This information is only held on newsletter subscribers who submitted it when a download offer was attached to the opt-in process.Information that newsletter subscribers may have provided when opting in to receive our newsletter only. Typically this is limited to Name and Email Address.Information that MailChimp determines on its own from newsletter subscribers’ activity, such as IP-based location (latitude/longitude, timezone, and country).We do not sell or rent this information, and only use it at times on an aggregated and anonymous basis to determine general data about our newsletter subscriber audience.The only time we share any newsletter subscriber information is when our subscribers download a piece of sponsored content from our site. In that case, we share the registrant data with the company(ies) that sponsored the download. Users are always notified prior to requesting the download that the information they submit will be shared with the sponsor.Paid ProductsWe have access to information you provided when purchasing a paid product, such as a report. This is limited to information necessary to process your payment, such as name, address and credit card information.This information is held by the entities that process it according to their terms of service.Managing Your DataYou can request to see the data we hold on you at any point, and you can also request deletion of your data at any point.Please email editorial@marketingcharts.com for any questions related to your personal data.Opt-in and Opt-OutWe make it easy for you to manage your email subscriptions, update your personal data, or unsubscribe. Inertia is a nice business helper, but we’re not interested in keeping you subscribed against your will. The primary way to unsubscribe is by clicking on automatic links generated at the bottom of each email newsletter. This is also the way to change your email address: unsubscribe with the link at the bottom, and re-subscribe with the subscribe link found at the top of the newsletter.If you use our “send story to a friend” feature, we won’t use your friend’s email for any other purpose. In fact we “fire and forget” and don’t collect these e-mails.If you post a comment on our site, we won’t use your email except to send you update notices about the specific entry you commented, or to initiate a private one-to-one email conversation with you about your post.Logging, Cookies, Web Beacons and Third Party AdvertisingWe collect anonymous usage data (technically known as “referrer logs”) on our web site, such as IP address, referrer site, or browser type. We do not link IP data to personal identification information except, when appropriate, for logged-on members to prevent account sharing fraud.We may use technical tracking means such as cookies or web beacons (single-pixel transparent gifs). These techniques are anonymous and used for statistical purposes only (e.g. finding our email open rate). We won’t try to monitor your anonymous personal usage of our site and letters. You can set up your browser to refuse cookies if you want to, though that might limit some site features.We use Google Analytics software to collect general information about how our audience uses MarketingCharts.com.We may use an outside advertising company to display advertisements on our website. Advertisements served from third parties may or may not contain cookies and other tracking mechanisms.SecurityWe have put security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Only authorized personnel are allowed physical and/or digital access to servers and data. All servers and data backups are kept secure from physical and electronic intrusion by use of firewalls and redundant security systems, which are periodically evaluated and upgraded.Legal DisclaimerPersonally Identifiable Information provided to Marketing Charts LLC is subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants or orders. We make every effort possible to preserve user privacy and anonymity; however, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein such action is necessary to comply with judicial proceedings, court orders or legal processes served on our Website.— Marketing Charts LLC, 2018This Privacy Policy was most recently updated on May 24, 2018.7ads6x98y
Email Address *
Subscribe to Our Newsletter
Error: Please enter a valid email addressError: Invalid emailError: Please enter your first nameError: Please enter your last nameError: Please enter a usernameError: Please enter a passwordError: Please confirm your passwordError: Password and password confirmation do not match
Download NowPin It on Pinterest
Share This
Facebook
Twitter
Pinterest
LinkedIn
About UsDigital StoreServicesContact UsPrivacy PolicyLicensing, Copyright & Fair Use Policy
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. By continuing to use our website, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.AcceptNoPrivacy PolicyRevoke Cookies
